Play or die.
Grand Piano is a thriller, mystery film directed by Eugenio Mira.
Tom Selznick, the most talented pianist of his generation, stopped
performing in public because of his stage fright.
Years after a catastrophic performance, he reappears in
public in a long awaited concert in Chicago.
Just moments after starting his performance in the packed theater, in front of an expectant audience,
Tom finds a threatening message written on the score: 'Play one wrong note and you die'.
Without leaving the piano, Tom must discover the anonymous sniper's
motives and look for help without anyone realizing.
Tom Selznick, played by Elijah Wood.
Clem, played by John Cusack.
Ashley, played by Tamsin Egerton.
Wayne, played by Allen Leech.
Emma Selznick, played by Kerry Bishé.
Assistant, played by Alex Winter.
Grand Piano is a 2013 Spanish English-language thriller film directed by Eugenio Mira,
written by Damien Chazelle, and starring Elijah Wood and John Cusack.
The film is about a once-promising pianist returning for a comeback performance, only to
be the target of a sniper who will kill him if he plays one wrong note.
The film premiered at Fantastic Fest on 20 September 2013 and
was given a VOD release on 30 January 2014.
It was given a limited release in American theatres on 7 March.
Grand Piano was Alex Winter's first non-cameo film role since 1993's Freaked.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois, sniper,
threat of death, stage fright, live performance.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.